<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>projects on Huy Le</title><link>https://www.huynle.com/projects/</link><description>Recent content in projects on Huy Le</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Apr 2017 07:03:20 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.huynle.com/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Home Renovation</title><link>https://www.huynle.com/projects/home-renovation/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.huynle.com/projects/home-renovation/</guid><description>[TOC]
Garage Note about garage fire &amp;lsquo;separationj&amp;rsquo;fire separation Drywall ceiling in the garage needs to be 5/8&amp;rdquo; Type &amp;ldquo;X&amp;rdquo; So this means no return air registers or heat supply registers inside the garage. garage door To meet fire separation requirements, the door must be one of three types of doors: a solid wood door not less than 1-3/8 inches thick, a solid or honeycomb core steel doors not less than 1-3/8 inches thick, or a 20-&amp;gt;minute fire-rated door, with a self-closing device.</description></item><item><title>Sainsmart RYC GRBL V2 Upgrade</title><link>https://www.huynle.com/projects/sainsmart-ryc-grbl-v2-upgrade/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2019 22:43:29 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://www.huynle.com/projects/sainsmart-ryc-grbl-v2-upgrade/</guid><description>GRBL has been optimized for Ardunio's ATmega328p. So most configurations out there will use the Arduino Uno and a CNC shield. I decide to go with the Sainsmart RYC-GRBL-V2 hoping it would work out of the box.
The reason why this is a long post is because it didn't work out of the box.
To get it up and running these are the list of things I changed to get it working.</description></item><item><title>Theming</title><link>https://www.huynle.com/projects/theming/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Mar 2018 09:13:03 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://www.huynle.com/projects/theming/</guid><description>Getting Vim background to match with Tmux Use :hi to show all the colors for the current theme in vim
Sync Tmux colors to sync with Vim change of colors is synced with vim. So background changes have to be done in Vim.</description></item><item><title>Initial Configs</title><link>https://www.huynle.com/projects/initial-configs/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2017 11:04:49 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.huynle.com/projects/initial-configs/</guid><description>Initial vim configurations. Played around and finally settled on Rafi's vim-config on GitHub. It had configurations for NeoVim as well as vim, and it had all the little things I was looking for when setting up Vim initially.
Checkout his configurations - https://github.com/rafi/vim-config
What is Dein? and Denite? Dein is a Vim package mananger. How does it work?
Reading log messages :messages will show the messages
What is Deoplete Completion!</description></item><item><title>Upgrade K8200 Controller Board</title><link>https://www.huynle.com/projects/upgrade-k8200-controller-board/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2016 17:47:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.huynle.com/projects/upgrade-k8200-controller-board/</guid><description>I realized it takes a very long time for the heated-bed to get up to temperature and start printing. This was one of the main reason why I did not use it as often as I originally intended.
With a slew of difficulties, e.g. Z-wobble and first layer not adhering to the board. The K8200 soon became a project of it's own. In short, this is the start to making the K8200 be usable, as an everyday tool.</description></item><item><title>Blogging</title><link>https://www.huynle.com/projects/blogging/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.huynle.com/projects/blogging/</guid><description>Todo: add search to static page Hosting blog github to gitlab
Using bootstrap dropdown menu editting with hackmd embedding hackmd notes</description></item><item><title>Custom Vim</title><link>https://www.huynle.com/projects/custom-vim/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.huynle.com/projects/custom-vim/</guid><description>The more I use Vim! The better I like it!
I've been messing around with Notepad++, Atom for awhile for my text editing needs. Atom was especially nice with all the the packages you can install. Something that was definitely noteworthy is PlatformIO for my Arduino code editing.
But at the end of the day I needed an editor, that allows me to write all my codes and edit my blogs.</description></item><item><title>DJI Flamewheel 450</title><link>https://www.huynle.com/projects/dji-flamewheel-450/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.huynle.com/projects/dji-flamewheel-450/</guid><description>As I stepped back into the UAV world from a couple years of break, the industry have grown significant from when I graduated school.
In this section, you will find posts about modifications to the DJI Flamewheel 450 frame that enables me to tinker with the PX4 autopilot.</description></item><item><title>Go Tunneling</title><link>https://www.huynle.com/projects/go-tunneling/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.huynle.com/projects/go-tunneling/</guid><description>Need to add &amp;ldquo;layout: project&amp;rdquo; to frontmatter for this page to show up!
Getting golang project ready
References: http://blog.ralch.com/tutorial/golang-ssh-tunneling/</description></item><item><title>iLawn</title><link>https://www.huynle.com/projects/ilawn/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.huynle.com/projects/ilawn/</guid><description>I need something to mow my lawn for me.
Initial Requirements: Shall cut the backyard lawn by itself Shall be using a gas powered mower Owner shall start the lawn mower itself Robot shall not cross the boundary between lawn and mulch Cost Estimate Used lawn mower at Good will - $~</description></item><item><title>K40-Laser</title><link>https://www.huynle.com/projects/k40-laser/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.huynle.com/projects/k40-laser/</guid><description>The K40 is a typical 40-Watt Chinese laser that most laser enthusiast and hobbyist would have in their arsenal. While it is fun to play with, my initial goal of getting this laser is to prepare for my upcoming wedding in a couple of month. Looking around the web for party favor and other wedding related items, everything can add up very fast. So by getting this cheap Chinese laser, we are hoping to cut down the cost of our wedding, but also have a useful tool for the long term.</description></item><item><title>K8200</title><link>https://www.huynle.com/projects/k8200/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.huynle.com/projects/k8200/</guid><description>It's time to upgrade the K8200!
I purchased the 8200 in 2014. I was looking to use it as a tool for my projects. It works for its intended purpose, but it did not work well. Each time printing, it was a bit of a hassle getting all the right variables.
In an attempt to make printer a little more user friendly, I did modifications to make my life a little easier.</description></item><item><title>Keysight Oscilloscope</title><link>https://www.huynle.com/projects/keysight-oscilloscope/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.huynle.com/projects/keysight-oscilloscope/</guid><description>Start of keysight remote data collection project!
Setting Up Get the IP address from the scope 10.21.45.67 Modules In Keysight Connection Expert Interactive IO enter in commands, send, and read response IO Monitor Command Expert Web UI Setting up Commands Software I/O Layers VISA and VISA COM are the new development standards, SICL is proprietary
Building the Application http://literature.</description></item><item><title>Learning C++</title><link>https://www.huynle.com/projects/learning-c-/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.huynle.com/projects/learning-c-/</guid><description>This is the start of a C++ journey</description></item></channel></rss>