<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>projects on Huy Le</title><link>https://www.huynle.com/projects/</link><description>Recent content in projects on Huy Le</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Apr 2017 07:03:20 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.huynle.com/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Streamline Converting EMR</title><link>https://www.huynle.com/streamline-converting-emr/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 21:08:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.huynle.com/streamline-converting-emr/</guid><description>Let&amp;rsquo;s convert all physical medical records to electronics
Objective Convert and maintain EMR for local medical offices
To-Do&amp;rsquo;s - Read on EMR - Electronic Medical Records - Find out how medical records are being kept - Identify some roadblocks - Extra - Read human genome project - Figure out how each patience is being tracked through this whole genome project - Are the there any open source places for medical record?</description></item><item><title>Blogging</title><link>https://www.huynle.com/blogging/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 18:50:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.huynle.com/blogging/</guid><description>Todo: add search to static page Hosting blog github to gitlab
Using bootstrap dropdown menu editting with hackmd embedding hackmd notes</description></item><item><title>Go Tunneling</title><link>https://www.huynle.com/go-tunneling/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 18:50:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.huynle.com/go-tunneling/</guid><description>Need to add &amp;ldquo;layout: project&amp;rdquo; to frontmatter for this page to show up!
Getting golang project ready
References: http://blog.ralch.com/tutorial/golang-ssh-tunneling/</description></item><item><title>TODO</title><link>https://www.huynle.com/todo/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 19:09:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.huynle.com/todo/</guid><description>My To-Do&amp;rsquo;s All the things that needs to be checked of
Unsorted To-do&amp;rsquo;s Install Let&amp;rsquo;s Encrypt on QNAP Write code for midicontroller Learn how to use Ansible to setup dotfiles convert tiddlywiki to markdown - https://github.com/achabotl/tiddly2md Look at Open Source Matlab &amp;ndash; https://www.gnu.org/software/octave/ Read on EMR - Electronic Medical Records Learn how to compile a Linux Kernel Project To-Do&amp;rsquo;s - Clean up Hizzle blog and get an updated version up and running - Set up a blog for Claire to journal/track General Development Tasks - Get esp-open-sdk up and running - Successfully build it and set PATH is a clean manner [o] - Get cscope up and running with VIM and a sample esp project - Get cscope and ctags to work with gutentags - Get cscope to ignore README and tags file.</description></item><item><title>Home Renovation</title><link>https://www.huynle.com/home-renovation/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.huynle.com/home-renovation/</guid><description>[TOC]
Garage Note about garage fire &amp;lsquo;separationj&amp;rsquo;fire separation Drywall ceiling in the garage needs to be 5/8&amp;rdquo; Type &amp;ldquo;X&amp;rdquo; So this means no return air registers or heat supply registers inside the garage. garage door To meet fire separation requirements, the door must be one of three types of doors: a solid wood door not less than 1-3/8 inches thick, a solid or honeycomb core steel doors not less than 1-3/8 inches thick, or a 20-&amp;gt;minute fire-rated door, with a self-closing device.</description></item><item><title>Shower Pan</title><link>https://www.huynle.com/shower-pan/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.huynle.com/shower-pan/</guid><description>Shower Pan Construction Material Needed Shower rough valve Framing and Plumbing Shower Pan Shower pan use packed dry mud on bottom layer
5 to 1 mixture of sand and Portland cement
clay like mixture that hold its shape when packed Top mortar layer should be 1 1/2&amp;rdquo; - 2&amp;rdquo; thick at the drain
Notes about different layers of mortars
Thin is a recipe for failure.</description></item><item><title>Keysight Oscilloscope</title><link>https://www.huynle.com/keysight-oscilloscope/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2017 19:06:43 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.huynle.com/keysight-oscilloscope/</guid><description>Start of keysight remote data collection project!
Setting Up Get the IP address from the scope 10.21.45.67 Modules In Keysight Connection Expert Interactive IO enter in commands, send, and read response IO Monitor Command Expert Web UI Setting up Commands Software I/O Layers VISA and VISA COM are the new development standards, SICL is proprietary
Building the Application http://literature.</description></item></channel></rss>