<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>essentials on Huy Le</title><link>https://www.huynle.com/categories/essentials/</link><description>Recent content in essentials on Huy Le</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2016 21:11:07 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.huynle.com/categories/essentials/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>SQL Basics</title><link>https://www.huynle.com/learnings/sql-basics/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2016 21:11:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.huynle.com/learnings/sql-basics/</guid><description>Introduction Relational databases are made from tables
SQL Standards
Code and Jargon Notes ; terminator and can be optional for some Dialects. also use as separator CAP vs cap SQL is not case sensitive. But to be portable, use &amp;lsquo;CAP&amp;rsquo; CODE here; -- comment here More recent SQL systems allow for &amp;ldquo;c-style&amp;rdquo; commenting /* comment */ for multiline Clauses are bite size code of a statement SELECT * FROM table -&amp;gt; clause 1; WHERE condition -&amp;gt; clause 2; Functions -&amp;gt; eg.</description></item><item><title>Starting NodeJS</title><link>https://www.huynle.com/learnings/starting-nodejs/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2016 21:11:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.huynle.com/learnings/starting-nodejs/</guid><description>What is node Up and Running A new key distinctions
nvm - Node version manager node - this is the main node engine npm - node package manager ~/.npmrc - configuration changes from global These three items are key to keeping a node environment together! It should be &amp;lsquo;noded&amp;rsquo; (lol), that there is a reason why nvm was created in the first place. This may be because the node engine changes from one revision to the next so often that manager is needed.</description></item><item><title>Learning SSH</title><link>https://www.huynle.com/learnings/learning-ssh/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Feb 2016 20:14:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.huynle.com/learnings/learning-ssh/</guid><description>What is SSH It is probably one of the most useful tools I have come to learn. Secure Shell is a protocol that allows data to be transferred securely between client and server. Typically, the client (typically is you) to log onto a server (another computer) remotely.
uses a pair of private and public keys.
These keys can be generated by a SSH key generator. There are different levels of security.</description></item></channel></rss>