<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Learnings on Huy Le</title><link>https://www.huynle.com/learnings/</link><description>Recent content in Learnings on Huy Le</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2020 20:01:13 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.huynle.com/learnings/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Scratchpad</title><link>https://www.huynle.com/scratchpad/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 15:11:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.huynle.com/scratchpad/</guid><description>Home Network QNAP Container station
Virtualization station
gatekeeper (sesame) Gate for access from outside world to LAN hassio - ubuntu server using to serve hassio, potentially more servers pfSense hassio Installing hassio https://community.home-assistant.io/t/my-way-to-install-hassio-on-qnap-nas/92257
Hugo JS and HTML interaction Hugo directory structure Note that when you are using shortcode, and that shortcode uses a JSscript sitting the the static page Makesure you import that JS script as an absolute path</description></item><item><title>Embedded Scratchpad</title><link>https://www.huynle.com/embedded-scratchpad/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 18:24:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.huynle.com/embedded-scratchpad/</guid><description>Contents [Embedded Things to Consider](#Embedded Things to Consider) [Tools](#Embedded Things to Consider#Tools) [Potential Issues with Embedded](#Embedded Things to Consider#Potential Issues with Embedded) [Memory Management](#Embedded Things to Consider#Memory Management) [Mutex vs Semaphores](#Embedded Things to Consider#Mutex vs Semaphores) [Debugging Embedded Systems - Link here](#Embedded Things to Consider#Debugging Embedded Systems - Link here) [Examples](#Embedded Things to Consider#Examples) Resources Embedded Things to Consider Extremely useful article - https://www.</description></item><item><title>Getting Nvidia GPU to work on Ubuntu</title><link>https://www.huynle.com/getting-nvidia-gpu-to-work-on-ubuntu/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 18:24:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.huynle.com/getting-nvidia-gpu-to-work-on-ubuntu/</guid><description>THIS IS THE MOST IMPORTANT ARTICLE TO READ!
https://devblogs.nvidia.com/gpu-containers-runtime/ The basics of Dockers docker images - the actual file for the container, this shows all the images that have been downloaded docker containers - the instance of the images docker ps -a - list all the containers, even the ones that are stopped docker start &amp;lt;container-name&amp;gt; - will start a stopped container docker stop &amp;lt;container-name&amp;gt; - will stop a running container the --rm - argument will destroy the container as soon as it is stopped Docker compose docker-compose up - spin up a docker container using docker-compose.</description></item><item><title>Manjaro Linux</title><link>https://www.huynle.com/manjaro-linux/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.huynle.com/manjaro-linux/</guid><description>TO-DO set up KVM for and check out VirtualGL performance install nvidia graphic driver share home drive with QNAP same user name and permission on NAS? ANSWER is LDAP! [QNAP LDAP]](https://www.qnap.com/en/how-to/tutorial/article/how-to-use-the-built-in-ldap-server-of-qnap-nas-for-user-management/) Configuration notes sudo access by other user on the files Todo: - push local user to ldap server - set nfs mount for home drive Sync user creation from qnap to machines draw network map https://github.</description></item><item><title>Installing Linux on Pixelbook</title><link>https://www.huynle.com/installing-linux-on-pixelbook/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.huynle.com/installing-linux-on-pixelbook/</guid><description>Understanding Linux Kernel - Low level drivers that interacts with hardware
Firmware Stuff Firmware Write Protect Firmware is stored on a special SPI flash chip and has a special register that sets the device to read-only. This change be changed by special hardware and software measures.
The write protection of these chips are dependent on grounding a WP pin on the flash chip.
Specific to chromebook models after 2017+ (CR50 models), the state of the WP pin is controlled by the CR50 with close-case debugging (CCD).</description></item><item><title>SSL Protocol</title><link>https://www.huynle.com/ssl-protocol/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2017 04:42:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.huynle.com/ssl-protocol/</guid><description>Introduction Encryption use cryptographic pair, composed of a key and a certificate. Root pair is a cryptographic pair that is used to sign intermediates CAs.
Handshake SSL handshake uses asymmetric encryption first, then symmetric encryption after. Reason being, symmetric encryption is a lot faster.
Client Action Server &amp;lsquo;Hello, these are encryption protocol I support&amp;hellip;&amp;rsquo; =&amp;gt; - - &amp;lt;= 'Hello, let&amp;rsquo;s use ___ protocol.</description></item><item><title>Starting NodeJS</title><link>https://www.huynle.com/starting-nodejs/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2016 21:11:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.huynle.com/starting-nodejs/</guid><description>What is node Up and Running A new key distinctions
nvm - Node version manager node - this is the main node engine npm - node package manager ~/.npmrc - configuration changes from global These three items are key to keeping a node environment together! It should be &amp;lsquo;noded&amp;rsquo; (lol), that there is a reason why nvm was created in the first place. This may be because the node engine changes from one revision to the next so often that manager is needed.</description></item><item><title>Git Workflow</title><link>https://www.huynle.com/git-workflow/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.huynle.com/git-workflow/</guid><description>Merging vs. Rebasing The two essentially do the same thing. the difference is that rebase makes the history linear. This is good when you are developing on your own branches, but not good when we you working on public branch, more here
To merge or rebase master into a feature
git checkout feature git merge master # or.. a oneliner git merge master feature # say it in your head, git merge master into feature Rewriting history keeping a clean history is important This code snippets will allow you to interactively update commits for a particular branch.</description></item></channel></rss>