<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Outdoor on Huy Le</title><link>https://www.huynle.com/categories/outdoor/</link><description>Recent content in Outdoor on Huy Le</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2016 06:41:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.huynle.com/categories/outdoor/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>You Are My Source</title><link>https://www.huynle.com/you-are-my-source/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2016 06:41:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.huynle.com/you-are-my-source/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s surprising how often You come to the rescue! Just when I am ready to checkout and give in, You deliver, time and time again!
It has been so consistent that my hope grows in You with each new day. And I thank you for that. For when trouble comes my way&amp;hellip; I know You will deliver!</description></item><item><title>The Maroon Bells</title><link>https://www.huynle.com/the-maroon-bells/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2013 05:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.huynle.com/the-maroon-bells/</guid><description>&lt;p>Trip to Montana? Nawh! I&amp;rsquo;ll do you one better! The Colorado Maroon Bells!
Sit down. Take a deep breath. I&amp;rsquo;ll tell a story&amp;hellip; &lt;/p></description></item><item><title>I'm Back!</title><link>https://www.huynle.com/im-back/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2013 23:08:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.huynle.com/im-back/</guid><description>In the spirit of anticipating for the start of the summer&amp;hellip; This another attempt to capture the stunning Delicate Arch!</description></item><item><title>Don't Plan... Cause You Won't Be Disappointed!</title><link>https://www.huynle.com/dont-plan...-cause-you-wont-be-disappointed/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2013 05:47:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.huynle.com/dont-plan...-cause-you-wont-be-disappointed/</guid><description>&lt;p>Have you ever spent $30 bucks on McDonald’s for four people. Maybe you have… maybe you haven’t. But the thing is… we just wanted to drop by a pick up a ‘small’ snack before we feast in Moab celebrating our conquering of Zion.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Zion - Conquered</title><link>https://www.huynle.com/zion-conquered/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2013 05:04:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.huynle.com/zion-conquered/</guid><description>&lt;p>Arrived at the trailhead, we eagerly jumped out of the shuttle to start our adventure. Meanwhile we were doing our last gear check, a couple next to us (the only other people that rode with us to the trailhead on the shuttle) started talking and got into a small conversation. The only memorable thing about our little chat was when the gal said “… we don’t plan for our trips, that way, we would never be disappointed.”&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Zion National Park</title><link>https://www.huynle.com/zion-national-park/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2013 01:37:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.huynle.com/zion-national-park/</guid><description>&lt;p>A week well before spring break, we had our gears ready and food prepared. On the Saturday before spring break starts, the four of us took off to Zion National Park. &lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Adventure - Defined</title><link>https://www.huynle.com/adventure-defined/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2013 04:27:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.huynle.com/adventure-defined/</guid><description>&lt;p>With that definition out of the way. Let&amp;rsquo;s talk about our adventure to the Great Sand Dunes eh?&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>We Came. We Saw. We Conquered.</title><link>https://www.huynle.com/we-came.-we-saw.-we-conquered./</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2013 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.huynle.com/we-came.-we-saw.-we-conquered./</guid><description>&lt;p>Lets pick up where we left off eh?
Moab. The one place where boys go to become men.. and girls to become boys.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>It's About the Journey, Not the Destination</title><link>https://www.huynle.com/its-about-the-journey-not-the-destination/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2013 08:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.huynle.com/its-about-the-journey-not-the-destination/</guid><description>&lt;p>Once again&amp;hellip; we found the adrenaline rush just sitting around and planning for a backpacking trip. This time, Moab, round two.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Father, Lead Me, I Can't Do this Alone</title><link>https://www.huynle.com/father-lead-me-i-cant-do-this-alone/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Sep 2012 05:09:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.huynle.com/father-lead-me-i-cant-do-this-alone/</guid><description>For the days that we were in Moab, we relied on these rocks that are stacked together by the people who have came before us to lead the way. These rocks are called, cairn. This is of a cave at the end of joint trail, completely filled with cairn.</description></item><item><title>Here's to the 14ers</title><link>https://www.huynle.com/heres-to-the-14ers/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Sep 2012 05:07:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.huynle.com/heres-to-the-14ers/</guid><description>This was taken a few weeks back when we went to hit up my first 14ers. It was shot at 5 in the morning on the way up to Mt. Beirdstadt (which is the peak on the right hand side). Here you can see the Sawtooth (in the middle) and Mt. Evans (on the left).</description></item><item><title>Keep Your Head Up</title><link>https://www.huynle.com/keep-your-head-up/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Sep 2012 04:42:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.huynle.com/keep-your-head-up/</guid><description>Some times we all look forward/down too much, keep your head up and you&amp;rsquo;ll be surprised. This is of a small little waterfall that feeds into Hanging Lake!</description></item><item><title>Modern Jungle</title><link>https://www.huynle.com/modern-jungle/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Sep 2012 04:37:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.huynle.com/modern-jungle/</guid><description>This was taken from a hotel room on my interview&amp;hellip; thought I was going to LA. But found out when I stepped foot on the plane that I was going to Louisiana. There is definitely a big difference between the two.</description></item><item><title>Life's Awaiting</title><link>https://www.huynle.com/lifes-awaiting/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Sep 2012 04:34:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.huynle.com/lifes-awaiting/</guid><description>This is of my little cousin from Texas taking on a blue run for her first time being on the slope. She&amp;rsquo;s a fast learner and got down with minimal damages!</description></item><item><title>Welcome to the West</title><link>https://www.huynle.com/welcome-to-the-west/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2012 06:29:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.huynle.com/welcome-to-the-west/</guid><description>&lt;p>Just this past weekend, our TNTT chapter went to the first ever Knights of Eucharist convention. With eight regions of TNTT that makes up the 1000+ people at the convention, our chapter is part of the West side. Otherwise known as.. Mien Tay. &lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Sit with Me Awhile</title><link>https://www.huynle.com/sit-with-me-awhile/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2012 17:03:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.huynle.com/sit-with-me-awhile/</guid><description>This is a self-picture from a morning hike in The Needles in Canyonlands National Park during sunrise.</description></item><item><title>Long Way Home</title><link>https://www.huynle.com/long-way-home/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2012 04:39:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.huynle.com/long-way-home/</guid><description>This is a scene from Hanging Lake. This was taken on the Dead Horse trail.. After hiking this trail, we found out why it was named the Dead Horse. And no.. there was no dead horse at the end of the trail, it was more of.. a trail that had steep loose jagged rocks that was nearly impossible to go up and was impossible to go back down. The best part was that the trail stopped and there was no clear path.</description></item><item><title>40 Years, Try 40 Hours</title><link>https://www.huynle.com/40-years-try-40-hours/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2012 14:22:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.huynle.com/40-years-try-40-hours/</guid><description>Just this past weekend, our youth group finished a camping trip. The camp was given a name, &amp;lsquo;Survival In Christ&amp;rsquo;. The theme is based off of the Book of Exodus and the 40 years that the Israelites spent in the desert. It was ironic how the Israelites spent 40 years in the desert, and we spent 40 hours in the hot summer sun. Through these 40 hours, there were blood, sweat and tear, literally.</description></item><item><title>Moab, Utah</title><link>https://www.huynle.com/moab-utah/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Jun 2012 16:18:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.huynle.com/moab-utah/</guid><description>&lt;p>We spend months before that Monday of Memorial Day, thinking about the trip, gathering up the gears and getting people to be on the same boat. It was determined that no matter what happened, the trip will be started and finished that week.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>