<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Journal on Huy Le</title><link>https://www.huynle.com/private/journal/</link><description>Recent content in Journal on Huy Le</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2020 19:48:39 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.huynle.com/private/journal/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>testing</title><link>https://www.huynle.com/private/journal/2018-04-17/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.huynle.com/private/journal/2018-04-17/</guid><description>Today&amp;rsquo;s Diary!
First Vimwiki Diary! This is just a start</description></item><item><title/><link>https://www.huynle.com/private/journal/2018-04-19/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.huynle.com/private/journal/2018-04-19/</guid><description/></item><item><title/><link>https://www.huynle.com/private/journal/2018-04-20/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.huynle.com/private/journal/2018-04-20/</guid><description>Notes Set compiler executable to some local binary path This might need to live in $HOME/.local/ directory ESP RTOS tagging setup The esp-open-rtos source directory is set up in away where Gutentags and vim is working out well The SDK is at the roots of the projects, this allows tags to always be generated So this means toolchains is at the root of the projects To Do Figure out a way to build the esp-open-sdk projects &amp;ndash; write it down!</description></item><item><title/><link>https://www.huynle.com/private/journal/2018-06-16/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.huynle.com/private/journal/2018-06-16/</guid><description>Start up idea of parking pods.
Requirements Pods shall be able to locate itself relative to one another, including 3D space Pods shall be able to run on battery for TBD amount of time Pods shall be software-serviceable, for software updates Pods shall be able be able to detect a vehicle/motocyle in the parking spot Pods shall be able to communicate to one another Pods shall be able to be durable against tampering and vandalism Pods shall be connected to its network with redundancy Pods shall be able to communicate to with a local nearby pod with minimum of TBD feet Pods shall be abla to</description></item><item><title/><link>https://www.huynle.com/private/journal/2018-06-28/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.huynle.com/private/journal/2018-06-28/</guid><description>TODO Today! Get ESP32 environment up and running for development Research on technology for mesh communication Check into the possiblity of Wifi, xbee, etc &amp;hellip; Prepare a presentation on Parking technology Come up with a list of collaboration apps Notes for today Vim setup for ESP32 and other embedded projects Need to find a way to import all the libraries for tagging ESP32 Setup today Getting gutentags to work with gtags?</description></item></channel></rss>