<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Thoughts on Huy Le</title><link>https://www.huynle.com/thoughts/</link><description>Recent content in Thoughts on Huy Le</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 18:50:39 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.huynle.com/thoughts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Thoughts</title><link>https://www.huynle.com/thoughts/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 18:50:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.huynle.com/thoughts/</guid><description>This is my thought page. There are time where I just want sit down and be able to write my thoughts to share with no structure.</description></item><item><title>Shared Simple Account</title><link>https://www.huynle.com/shared-simple-account/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2019 11:18:43 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://www.huynle.com/shared-simple-account/</guid><description>The CFO of the House Outline Transparency Setting goals together Struggling together How much do we have for this month</description></item><item><title>2017 Portland Marathon</title><link>https://www.huynle.com/2017-portland-marathon/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2017 07:09:26 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://www.huynle.com/2017-portland-marathon/</guid><description>Preparing for the Portland Marathon started about 6 months before. I was running before the registration, but on June 7th, 2017, I made a decision to run in the marathon. I have never ran a marathon before, and never even dreamed about running it. But after running with a close friend on a frequent basis, I got exposed to a technique that helped me through the training and the marathon itself.</description></item><item><title>Simple Banking</title><link>https://www.huynle.com/simple-banking/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2017 11:18:43 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://www.huynle.com/simple-banking/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m not sure about a lot of people, but I was constantly surprise by my credit card statement each month as I pay off my credit card. It is also no surprise that my savings, were really saving. When I have some extra money left over from my monthly spending, I throw in a dollar here and there just to have a saving. This was not working out.
The Envelope System - Digitized Goals are set up just like evelope Set a goal and the time you want to reach it Goals: Mortage for the month Food budget Fuel budget Groceries Eating out Pet budget Emergency funds Hobby/project funds Pick a budget, set a time and fund it!</description></item></channel></rss>