<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Essentials on Huy Le</title><link>https://www.huynle.com/learnings/essentials/</link><description>Recent content in Essentials on Huy Le</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 14:46:34 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.huynle.com/learnings/essentials/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>My Useful Commands</title><link>https://www.huynle.com/my-useful-commands/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 14:46:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.huynle.com/my-useful-commands/</guid><description>My Useful Commands Commands Notes Nothing grep -rin &amp;quot;text here&amp;quot; . For recursive text search, that is case insensitive with line numbers Standards In/Out/Error STDIN (channel 0): Where your command draws the input from.</description></item><item><title>Vim Essentials</title><link>https://www.huynle.com/vim-essentials/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2017 10:39:25 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://www.huynle.com/vim-essentials/</guid><description>There are so many things to talk about Vim, this article is aimed to help you get you familiar with Vim by learning what the basic features and ability of Vim.
After using Vim for about a year now, there are a few things I wish I knew about Vim when I first made the commitment to jump over to this ancient looking editor; let me tell you, this text editor is anything be ancient.</description></item><item><title>SQL Basics</title><link>https://www.huynle.com/sql-basics/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2016 21:11:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.huynle.com/sql-basics/</guid><description>Introduction Relational databases are made from tables
SQL Standards
Code and Jargon Notes ; terminator and can be optional for some Dialects. also use as separator CAP vs cap SQL is not case sensitive. But to be portable, use &amp;lsquo;CAP&amp;rsquo; CODE here; -- comment here More recent SQL systems allow for &amp;ldquo;c-style&amp;rdquo; commenting /* comment */ for multiline Clauses are bite size code of a statement SELECT * FROM table -&amp;gt; clause 1; WHERE condition -&amp;gt; clause 2; Functions -&amp;gt; eg.</description></item><item><title>Linux Essentials</title><link>https://www.huynle.com/linux-essentials/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2016 02:25:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.huynle.com/linux-essentials/</guid><description>Linux Filesystem You got your swap, root and home partitions
swap - space on the hard drive use for virtual memory root -
LVM - Logical Volume Management Setting up system for backup and imaging - wiki
Create a snapshot of the current logical volume sudo lvcreate --size 10G -s -n p_nodered /dev/ubuntu-vg/root Do any modification to the filesystem If everything works as expected, remove the snapshot. Keeping it from growing!</description></item></channel></rss>